(Stuart:)Raj, if it's
any consolation,
(Stuart:)I'm no better off than
I was ten years ago.
Oh, yay!
(Raj:)I have a doctorate
in astrophysics
(Raj:)and I'm every bit as awesome
(Raj:)as the pasty-faced owner
of a comic book store!
Raj! Show some compassion.
(Sheldon:)Those are things that
we think but don't say.
(Raj:)Excuse me.
(Leonard:)Sorry, Stuart.
(Stuart:)Hey, I'm in a hospital
and I'm not the patient.
(Stuart:)I'm fine.
(Howard:)Come on, Bernie, breathe.
(Howard:)Remember what you learned
in birthing class.
(Bernadette:)I remember thinking,
“This is stupid”"
and I was right!
(Howard:)Do you want me
to get the nurse?
No! If one more person puts
their fingers near my uterus,
(Bernadette:)I'm gonna cross my legs
and snap 'em off!
(Leonard:)I've come to peace with my
relationship with my parents.